[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]
Great, we've now seen the notion of overfitting in classification,
عظيم، لقد استعرضنا الآن فكرة التطابق المفرط في التصنيف،
especially logistic regression.
وخصوصًا الانحدار اللوجستي.
We've seen how decision boundaries get really complicated as we start
ولاحظنا كيف ان حدود القرار تصبح أكثر تعقيدًا
overfitting.
عند بدء التطابق المفرط.
How those parameter values tend to increase.
وكيف أن تلك المعلمات تميل للزيادة.
How we get overconfident about our predictions.
وكيف يمكننا اكتساب ثقة شديدة تجاه تنبؤاتنا.
We introduce the notion of regularization to try to
وقمنا بعرض فكرة التنظيم
mitigate blowing up of those parameters.
لمحاولة التخفيف من وقع هذه المعلمات.
By doing so, we've seen how they can take the ideas of logistic regression, which
ومن خلال القيام بذلك، يمكننا ملاحظة كيف يمكنها أخذ أفكار الانحدار اللوجستي،
were so far more on the theoretical side, into being ready for real practical work.
والذي كان يميل أكثر للجانب النظري، ليصبح مستعدًا للجانب العملي من العمل.
You should be able to take those ideas and implement them in practice
ويجب أن تكون قادرًا على أخذ تلك الأفكار وتطبيقها في الممارسة
using L2 regularization, and you'll also see how L1 regularization can make sense.
باستخدام تنظيم L2، وسيمكنك ملاحظة كيف أن تنظيم L1، يمكنه ان يكون منطقيًا،
We haven't described how to implement that, but it's similar to what you did for
ولم نتطرق لوصف كيف يمكن تطبيق ذلك،
the last problem before.
ولكنه يشبه ما قمنا به في المشكلة السابقة.
[MUSIC]
[موسيقى]